Okay!
Which one does NOT belong?
A.
Apple,
B.
Piano,
C.
Orange,
or D.
Mango?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
The answer is...
B,
piano!
An apple,
orange,
and mango are fruits.
A piano is an instrument,
so it does not belong.
Here's one,
a shape puzzle!
Which shape comes next?
A.
A circle,
B.
An octagon,
C.
A hexagon,
or D.
A square?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
The answer is...
C,
a hexagon!
The number of sides goes up
by one each step,
so the next shape is the hexagon.
Here's one,
a number series!
Four,
six,
ten,
sixteen,
twenty-six,
and then...
what comes next?
A.
Forty-three,
B.
Forty-four,
C.
Forty-two,
or D.
Fifty-two?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
The answer is...
C,
forty-two!
Add the two numbers before it:
twenty-six plus sixteen is forty-two.
So,
are you smart or fart?
Count up your correct answers to
find your rank!
So,
how did you do?
Comment your score below,
and follow for more!